{"response_code": 0, "results": [{"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Nintendo started out as a playing card manufacturer.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "&quot;Undertale&quot; is an RPG created by Toby Fox and released in 2015.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The game &quot;Battlefield 1&quot; takes place during World War I.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In Kingdom Hearts the Paopu fruit is said to intertwine the destinies for two people forever.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "TF2: The Heavy&#039;s voice actor, Gary Schwartz, voices the Demoman as well ", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Ana was added as a new hero for the game Overwatch on July 19th, 2016.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "David Baszucki was a co-founder of ROBLOX Corporation.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Watch_Dogs 2 is a prequel.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "&quot;Metal Gear Solid 3: Snake Eater&quot; was released in 2004.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "question": "The Paradox Interactive game &quot;Stellaris&quot; was released in 2016.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]}